HAFIZ LATIFF

Blk 10A #02-105 Bendemeer Road Singapore 331010

+65 81120424

fiz.latiff@gmail.com

Executive Summary

A multifaceted, highly motivated and detail oriented professional offering over 3 years of experience in the accounting and financial fields. Ability to work independently and as part of a team across challenging environments. Excellent interpersonal skills towards building relationships at all organizational levels and curious to learn.

Relevant Experience

Partners Group

Sep 2013 - Present

Fund Accountant, Financial Analyst

- · Handling full sets of accounts including monthly net asset value finalization and cash and portfolio reconciliation
- Investigating portfolio valuation analysis, accruals, amortization of prepayments, hedges and stock distribution valuation
- Maximizing productivity and increasing efficiency through orchestrating refreshers of fund accounting business processes
- Managing the accounts of more than 10 private equity, infrastructure and real estate funds over \$500 million in net asset valuation
- In charge of first in-house accounting for a mandate investing in various business segments including semi liquid funds
- Reviewing more than 12 funds and ensuring accurate assessments of the net asset valuation production on a monthly basis
- Analysing legal documents including but not limited to agreements, constituent documents and side letters of funds
- · Monitoring access vehicles reporting and blocker accounting which consist of leverage and non-leverage portfolios
- Preparation of monthly, quarterly and annual financial statements in accordance to International Financial Reporting Standard
- Coordinated and executed the calculation and integration of closing and management fees of several funds on a quarterly basis
- Engineered a schedule in the recruitment and supervision of new co-workers on the department's operations and systems
- · Interacted with Treasury department on reviewing and validating of cash flow transactions on underlying investments

The Development Bank of Singapore (DBS)

Aug 2012 - Dec 2012

Risk Management Group - Limit Control Unit, Bank Executive

- Facilitated in User Acceptance Testing (UAT) for various projects including preparation of statistical reports
- Consolidated record creation and updated static customer data in systems to facilitate activation of credit facilities

Suhaimi Salleh and Associates

Jun 2011 - Aug 2011

Audit Assistant, Internship

- · Examined company accounts and financial control systems by checking financial reports and records
- Conducted compliance testing and vouching of documents after collating, checking and analysing spreadsheet data
- · Reviewed corporation's internal controls to make certain procedures, policies and regulations were correctly complied with

National Trade Union Congress Income

Dec 2008 - Mar 2012

- Customer Relations Department, Operations Support Personnel
 - Provided customer service for initiation and renewal of various insurance schemes
 - Advised customer enquiries and handling of physical monies on a daily basis

Education

University of London

Aug 2009 - May 2013

• Bachelor of Science in Accounting & Finance

Catholic Junior College

Jan 2005 - Nov 2006

• General Certificate of Education Advance Level

St Gabriel's Secondary School

Jan 2001 - Nov 2004

• General Certificate of Secondary Education Ordinary Level

Skills

Software - Proficient in Microsoft Suite, eFront software and Abacus accounting software

Language - Proficient in English, Malay and Bahasa Indonesia. Basic command of Mandarin

Other Interests - Health and fitness, racket sports and reading